{
  "shortDescription": "Test your knowledge of food.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is sushi?",
      "answers": ["Fish", "Rice", "Soup"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is pizza?",
      "answers": ["Bread", "Pie", "Cake"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is tofu?",
      "answers": ["Soy", "Dairy", "Grain"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is guacamole?",
      "answers": ["Dip", "Soup", "Bread"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is ramen?",
      "answers": ["Noodles", "Rice", "Meat"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is taco?",
      "answers": ["Wrap", "Bread", "Rice"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is paella?",
      "answers": ["Rice", "Soup", "Bread"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is gelato?",
      "answers": ["Ice", "Cake", "Cookie"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is hummus?",
      "answers": ["Dip", "Bread", "Soup"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is baguette?",
      "answers": ["Bread", "Cake", "Pasta"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    }
  ]
}
